Lesson 14.
Amber and Ted heat up the kitchen.
Amber and Ted are in the kitchen baking cookies.
Amber asks Ted to give her a kiss, but Ted tells her he's too busy.
Then he feels guilty and goes to her.
But suddenly, they're not alone.
Ted, when I met you, it was love at first sight.
I was nuts about you from the beginning, too, Amber.
Don't forget, I broke up with that girl Tiffany after I met you.
Come here and give me a kiss.
Give me a break, Amber.
We don't have time for that now.
We need to crank out these cookies.
You don't really love me, do you?
Amber, I'm head over heels and love with you,
but it's crunch time with these cookies.
Cookies, cookies, cookies.
You've got a one-track mind.
He loves cookies, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Amber, I need to keep working, but you can take a break if you want.
No, I'll keep plugging away.
I'm just your cookie slave.
Go ahead, treat me like dirt.
Sorry, Amber, come here and let me give you a quick kiss.
Hey, what's going on in here?
Are you two making cookies or making out?